1. openBrowser("")
5. navigateToUrl(URL)
9. maximizeWindow()
13. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/header_digibox"))
17. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
21. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-account"), "agungpriyadi")
25. setText(findTestObject("Registration/field-Password"), "Laskar123456")
29. click(findTestObject("Login/btn-sign in"))
33. click(findTestObject("Registration/icon-acount"))
37. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/verify-succes-acount-login"))
41. click(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/icon-search"))
45. sendKeys(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/field-search"), Keys.chord("IPHONE 12 PRO MAX 128GB GOLD", ENTER))
49. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Home Page/Search/verify-product-iphone-12 -pro"))
53. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/btn-product - IPHONE 12 PRO MAX 128GB GOLD"))
57. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/button_Add to Cart"))
61. waitForElementPresent(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"), 10)
65. click(findTestObject("Product and Cart/Add to cart/i_icon-cart"))
69. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/btn_checkout"), 10)
73. click(findTestObject("Checkout/Address/btn_checkout"))